ILGWU. Irwin Solomon papers, 5780/187
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Unity House, 1965-1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Welfare Fund Control Study, 1980-1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Burt Conley, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Cloak and Dress Drivers and Helpers Union, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU General Fund, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  July
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Towers Perrin: UNITE Staff Retirement Plan First Quarter, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Susan Cowell [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Susan Cowell [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: Philadelphia Area, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia-South Jersey District Council, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Philadelphia Region, 1979-1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Solomon [folder 1 of 3], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Solomon [folder 2 of 3], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Solomon [folder 3 of 3], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Wilbur Daniels, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Perry Parker, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Solomon [folder 1 of 3], 1987 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Solomon [folder 2 of 3], 1987 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Solomon [folder 3 of 3], 1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Milton Spitz, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Gus Tyler, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Unity House: Legal, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Upper South, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Wang Computer, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Washington Office, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Welfare Control, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Wolf and Schulman, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Western States, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Xerox, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1997 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Accounting Statements, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  October
- UNITE General Fund Statements, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU General Fund, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Glickenhaus and Company: UNITE Portfolio Summary, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Goldman Sachs: Fixed Income Portfolio, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- J. P. Morgan: UNITE General Fund, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  October - November
- AFL-CIO, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Bank [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Bank [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Chuck Lauster, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Automobile Log: Solomon, 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Central States, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Chaikin and Chaikin, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Finance Committee, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Convention, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Deborah Heart and Lung Center, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Fashion Institute of Technology, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- General Fund, 1989-1991 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Investment Committee, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  March 8
- Pooled Investment Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Investment Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Lehman Ark Management, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Audit Department, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Convention [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Convention [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Investment Committee Meeting, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  March 30
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  May 8-11
- General Executive Board (GEB) Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Post-Merger [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Post-Merger [folder 2 of 2], 1995 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Pending Court Cases, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Regional Personnel Reports, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  March
- ACTWU/ILGWU Personnel, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- ACTWU/ILGWU Employee Benefits, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Dues, Per Capita Tax, and Initiation Fees, 1993-1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Balance Sheet Comparison, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Defense Fund/ILGWU Organizing and Strike Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- ACTWU/ILGWU: Organization Directory, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- ACTWU/ILGWU: Structure of Union (Box 41, Folder 2)
- ACTWU/ILGWU: Convention Delegates, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- ACTWU: LM Reports [folder 1 of 3], 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- ACTWU: LM Reports [folder 2 of 3], 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- ACTWU: LM Reports [folder 3 of 3], 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- ACTWU/ILGWU: Constitution Comparison, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Documents and Information Tables, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Service Employees International Union (SEIU): National Budget, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Staff Benefit Programs Comparison, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Arthur Loevy, 1990-1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Comparison of Personnel: General Office Only, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Member Benefit Programs Comparison (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR) and Local 153 Contracts, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Census Information, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Merger Committee (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR)/Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU) Contracts [folder 1 of 4], 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR)/Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU) Contracts [folder 2 of 4], 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR)/Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU) Contracts [folder 3 of 4], 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR)/Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU) Contracts [folder 4 of 4], 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) and International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Merger Announcement, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  February 20
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)/International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Constitution [folder 1 of 6], 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)/International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Constitution [folder 2 of 6], 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)/International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Constitution [folder 3 of 6], 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)/International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Constitution [folder 4 of 6], 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)/International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Constitution [folder 5 of 6], 1992-1995 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)/International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Constitution [folder 6 of 6], 1992-1995 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU): Regional Constitution and By-laws (Box 44, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Merger Information: Volume 1, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Merger Information: Volume 2, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Merger Information: Volume 3, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Merger Information: Volume 4, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Merger Information: Volume 5, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Bank [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Bank [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Auditing, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Automobile Logs, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Benefit Funds [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Benefit Funds [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Census Comparisons, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Central States Region, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Computer Department, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Deborah Hospital, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Eastern States, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board (GEB), 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- ILGWU General Fund, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Jewish Labor Committee Jewish Labor Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Leader Data Processing, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- National Retirement Fund Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- National Retirement Fund Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- ORT Federation, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Professional and Clerical Employees (PACE), 1987-1989 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Professional Employees, AFL-CIO, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Retiree Services, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Social Services Task Force, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Union Health Center [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Union Health Center [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Perry Parker, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Max Zimny, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Jay Mazur [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Jay Mazur [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Don Fischer, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Susan Cowell, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Western States, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Census Comparison, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Central States Region, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Central States Region: Paula Johnson, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Century Mills: A. H. Schreiber, 1982-1988 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Chase Manhattan Bank, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Marie Cloutier, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- City of Hope (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Co-Hop Meeting, 1986-1993 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Coopers and Lybrand, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Council for American Fashion (CAF), 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Council for Labor and Industry, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Court Cases, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Defense Personnel Support Center, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Devon Apparel, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Disaster Relief, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Domsey Strike (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Due from Affiliates, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Eastern States [folder 1 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Eastern States [folder 2 of 2], 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Roy and Christina Eaton, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Education, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Educational Foundation, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- African-American Labor Center, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Mallory Factor, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Fashion Apparel Manufacturers Association (FAMA), 1985-1988 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT), 1994 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Federal Funding Grants, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Felco, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Fund for Open Society, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Executive Session, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  October 24
- General Advisory Council, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  October 26
- Retirement Funds, 1987-1989 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Accounts Receivable, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Administrative Department, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Advanced Training Institute, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- All-State Insurance Proposal, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- American Auto Leasing Corporation, 1989-1994 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Labor, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Appeals (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Ark Asset Management, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Asbestos Removal, 1985-1988 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Associate Membership, 1985-1994 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Astoria Press, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA), 1988-1995 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Avon Boycott, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Bell Radio Taxi, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Blue Cross, 1989-1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Eva Bollinger, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Boston Pharmacy, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Bridal Originals, 1988-1990 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Bobbie Brooks, 1987-1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Budget, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Budget Reconciliation, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Council for American Fashion (CAF), 1992 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Calvin Klein, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Campaign Committee Contributions, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Canada, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Canadian Office, 1991-1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Canadian Office: Gerald Roy, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Canadian Office: Toronto, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Canadian Office: Merger Report (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Alex Dagg, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Toronto, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Toronto, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  October 15
- Toronto: Sale of Lyceum Shares, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Toronto: Tom Steers, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Montreal, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Montreal: Request for Charter, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Winnipeg: Spillet, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Alex Dagg, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Canada, 1984-1988 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Canada, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Canada Appeal: Gilles Gauthier, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Solomon Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Homework and Political Literature, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- General Office Budget, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- General Funds, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Health and Safety, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Histadrut, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Homework, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Imported Audit Bills, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Industrial Union Department, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Buck Consultants, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Justice, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Leader Data Processing, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Local 10, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Local 23-25, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Local 60-40, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Local 89-22-1, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Local 91-105, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Local 99, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Local 132-98, 1985-1987 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Local 102, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Local 155, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Midwest Region, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- National Retirement Fund, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- National Retirement Fund, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- National Retirement Fund, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- National Retirement Fund, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Death Benefit Fund, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Severance Funds [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Severance Funds [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- New England Region, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- New Jersey Region, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- New Jersey Region: New Building, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- New York State District, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Northeast Department, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Northeast Department: Retiree Letter, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Northeast Department: Restructuring, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Northeast Department: Dalton Industries, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Solomon: Personal [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Solomon: Personal [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- American Trade Union Council, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Amounts Due, 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- AMPAL Securities, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Arnold and Porter, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Auditing Department, 1986-1988 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Automobile Logs, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Benefits, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Canadian Office, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Current Census, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Central States Region, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Chaikin and Chaikin, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Collection Department, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Convention [folder 1 of 3], 1986 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Convention [folder 2 of 3], 1986 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Convention [folder 3 of 3], 1986 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Data Processing, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Deborah Hospital, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Education, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Engineering Department, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Executive Committee, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  March 17-20
- Financial Reports, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Epilepsy Center, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Mallory Factor, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Finance Department, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- General Advisory Council, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  February
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings and Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings and Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Staff Benefits, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings and Reports, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 1 of 7], 1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 2 of 7], 1988 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 3 of 7], 1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 4 of 7], 1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 5 of 7], 1988 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 6 of 7], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 7 of 7], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 1 of 3], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 2 of 3], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 3 of 3], 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 1 of 7], 1987 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 2 of 7], 1987 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 3 of 7], 1987 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 4 of 7], 1987 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 5 of 7], 1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 6 of 7], 1987 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Benefit Plan Taxes [folder 7 of 7], 1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 1 of 10], 1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 2 of 10], 1987 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 3 of 10], 1987 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 4 of 10], 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 5 of 10], 1987 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 6 of 10], 1987 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 7 of 10], 1987 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 8 of 10], 1987 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 9 of 10], 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Benefit Plan Statements [folder 10 of 10], 1987 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Benefit Funds, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Center Against Apartheid, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Chaikin and Chaikin, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- City Council of Philadelphia, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Claridge's London, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Co-Hop, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Collection Control Department, 1981-1984 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Easter Pennsylvania Region, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Finance, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings and Reports, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings and Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings and Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- General Mills, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Government Shops, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Union Health Center, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Union Health Center: Cyd Weldon, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Union Health Services, 1983-1984 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Hertz, 1982-1985 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Histadrut, 1983-1984 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Homework, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Canada, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- ILGWU General Financial Statements, 1983-1984 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Imports, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Investment Committee, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Sidney Vyorst Incorporated, 1973-1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Stratford Advisory Group, 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Just Plastic Incorporated, 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Leader Data Processing, 1982-1984 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Local 23-25, 1982-1986 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Local 66-40, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Local 91 Realty Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Local 98-132, 1984-1985 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Local 153, 1982-1985 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Local 155, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Local 190, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Invitations, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Plumbers Union Local 2, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Engineering Department, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- MCI Telephone, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Meetings, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Midwest Region, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- National Benefit Funds, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- NAACP Convention, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- National Retirement Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Newmark Real Estate, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- New Jersey Region, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- New England Region, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Non-assessable, 1968-1985 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- ORT, 1983-1985 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Personnel: Resumes, 1984-1986 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Sol Chaikin, 1982-1984 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Wilbur Daniels, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Lawrence Dock, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Jay Mazur, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Irwin Solomon, 1983-1986 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Milton Spitz, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Herman Starobin, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Gus Tyler [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Gus Tyler [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Staff Benefits, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Local 340A, 1993-1995 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Beck, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1996 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1996 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- UNITE/FOUR Agreements (Box 68, Folder 9)
- UNITE/OPEIU/Local 153 Agreement (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Study of Benefit Fund Programs, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Fleet Car Roster, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Golden Triangle Business Improvement District (BID), 1997 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Arnold and Porter, 1996-1998 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Szold and Brandwen, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board (GEB) Meetings, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- EPR-ILGWU Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Realty Holding Corporation Financial Statements, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Local 91 Realty Corporation Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Joint Board Dress Building Incorporated Financial Statements, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- 1710 Broadway Incorporated Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Report, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU General Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- J.P. Morgan: ILGWU General Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Bank: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 69, Folder 16)